<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on FILE - WIBU</title>
    <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on FILE - WIBU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 02:15:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://file-wibu.netlify.app/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kimi Wa Kanata</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kimi-wa-kanata/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 02:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kimi-wa-kanata/</guid>
      <description>JudulKimi wa Kanata Japanese君は彼方 Score6.55 ProduserCUCURI TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi1 hr 35 min Tanggal RilisNov 27, 2020 StudioDigital Network Animation GenreDrama, Fantasy   Mio has feelings for her childhood friend Arata, but can&#39;t convey her feelings. One day, as they continue their delicate relationship, the two fight over something trivial. After letting tensions settle, Mio goes to make up with him in the pouring rain. While on her way, she gets into a traffic accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ousama Ranking Dual Subs Indonesia &amp; English</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/ousama-ranking-dual-subs-indonesia-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 07:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/ousama-ranking-dual-subs-indonesia-english/</guid>
      <description>JudulOusama Ranking Japanese王様ランキング Score7.53 ProduserAniplex, Dentsu, Fuji TV, Kadokawa TipeTV StatusOngoing Total Episode23 Durasi23 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 15, 2021 to ? StudioWit Studio GenreAdventure, Fantasy   The web manga centers around Bojji, a deaf, powerless prince who cannot even wield a children&#39;s sword. As the firstborn son, he strives hard and dreams of becoming the world&#39;s greatest king. However, people mutter about him behind his back as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youjo Senki S1 BD Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/youjo-senki-s1-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 10:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/youjo-senki-s1-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulYoujo Senki Japanese幼女戦記 Score7.98 ProduserMedia Factory, AT-X, Enterbrain, Sony Music Communications TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode12 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisJan 6, 2017 to Mar 31, 2017 StudioNut GenreAction   Tanya Degurechaff is a young soldier infamous for predatorial-like ruthlessness and an uncanny, tactical aptitude, earning her the nickname of the &#34;Devil of the Rhine.&#34; Underneath her innocuous appearance, however, lies the soul of a man who challenged Being X, the self-proclaimed God, to a battle of wits—which resulted in him being reincarnated as a little girl into a world of magical warfare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shuumatsu No Harem Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/shuumatsu-no-harem-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/shuumatsu-no-harem-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulShuumatsu no Harem Japanese終末のハーレム Score6.62 ProduserUnknown TipeTV StatusOngoing Total Episode11 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 8, 2021 to ? StudioStudio Gokumi, AXsiZ GenreSci-Fi, Ecchi   The Man-Killer Virus: a lethal disease that has eradicated 99.9% of the world&#39;s male population. Mizuhara Reito has been in cryogenic sleep for the past five years, leaving behind Tachibana Erisa, the girl of his dreams. When Reito awakens from the deep freeze, he emerges into a sex-crazed new world where he himself is the planet&#39;s most precious resource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Kaito 1412 Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/magic-kaito-1412-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 07:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/magic-kaito-1412-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulMagic Kaito 1412 Japaneseまじっく快斗1412 Score7.86 ProduserAniplex, Yomiuri Telecasting, DAX Production TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode24 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 4, 2014 to Mar 28, 2015 StudioA-1 Pictures GenreAdventure, Comedy, Romance   Eight years after the mysterious death of his father, Kaito Kuroba, a slightly mischievous but otherwise ordinary teenager, discovers a shocking secret: the Phantom Thief Kaito Kid—also known as &#34;The Magician Under the Moonlight&#34;—was none other than his own father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JoJo No Kimyou Na Bouken Stardust Crusaders Subtitles indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/jojo-no-kimyou-na-bouken-stardust-crusaders-subtitles-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/jojo-no-kimyou-na-bouken-stardust-crusaders-subtitles-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulJoJo no Kimyou na Bouken Part 3: Stardust Crusaders Japaneseジョジョの奇妙な冒険 スターダストクルセイダース Score8.09 ProduserYomiko Advertising, Warner Bros. Japan, Kamikaze Douga, KlockWorx, Shueisha TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode24 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisApr 5, 2014 to Sep 13, 2014 StudioDavid Production GenreAction, Adventure, Drama, Supernatural   Years after an ancient evil was salvaged from the depths of the sea, Joutarou Kuujou sits peacefully within a Japanese jail cell. He&#39;s committed no crime yet demands he not be released, believing he&#39;s been possessed by an evil spirit capable of harming those around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akira 1988 BD Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/akira-1988-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 04:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/akira-1988-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulAkira JapaneseAKIRA（アキラ） Score8.16 ProduserMainichi Broadcasting System, Kodansha, Toho TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi2 hr 4 min Tanggal RilisJul 16, 1988 StudioTokyo Movie Shinsha GenreAction, Adventure, Horror, Sci-Fi, Supernatural   Japan, 1988. An explosion caused by a young boy with psychic powers tears through the city of Tokyo and ignites the fuse that leads to World War III. In order to prevent any further destruction, he is captured and taken into custody, never to be heard from again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getsuyoubi No Tawawa S2 Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/getsuyoubi-no-tawawa-s2-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 01:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/getsuyoubi-no-tawawa-s2-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulGetsuyoubi no Tawawa 2 Japanese月曜日のたわわ2 Score6.86 ProduserNBCUniversal Entertainment Japan TipeONA StatusOngoing Total Episode12 Durasi6 min per ep Tanggal RilisSep 20, 2021 to ? StudioYokohama Animation Lab GenreSlice of Life, Ecchi   The anime follows a salaryman who has a chance meeting with a girl named Ai on the train. They begin to meet every Monday on the train, with the man serving as her bodyguard on the crowded commute while they chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violet Evergarden Movie 2020 BD HEVC</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/violet-evergarden-movie-2020-bd-hevc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/violet-evergarden-movie-2020-bd-hevc/</guid>
      <description>JudulViolet Evergarden Movie Japanese劇場版 ヴァイオレット・エヴァーガーデン Score8.88 ProduserShochiku TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi2 hr 20 min Tanggal RilisSep 18, 2020 StudioKyoto Animation GenreDrama, Fantasy, Slice of Life   Several years have passed since the end of The Great War. As the radio tower in Leidenschaftlich continues to be built, telephones will soon become more relevant, leading to a decline in demand for &#34;Auto Memory Dolls.&#34; Even so, Violet Evergarden continues to rise in fame after her constant success with writing letters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kengan Ashura BATCH Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kengan-ashura-batch-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 12:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kengan-ashura-batch-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulKengan Ashura Japaneseケンガンアシュラ Score7.45 ProduserNihon Ad Systems, Mainichi Broadcasting System, Pony Canyon, Shogakukan, KLab, Netflix, MAGNET TipeONA StatusFinished Airing Total Episode12 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisJul 31, 2019 StudioLarx Entertainment GenreAction   Business deals are usually made through meetings and contracts; but in the world of Kengan Ashura, businesses resort to other means to make their decisions: by hiring gladiators. Yabako Sandrovich&#39;s Kengan Ashura depicts a world brimming with action, violence, and martial arts—one where powerful gladiators have fought in grand arenas since the Edo Period to settle the disputes of wealthy businesses and merchants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getsuyoubi No Tawawa S1 &#43;OVA BD Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/getsuyoubi-no-tawawa-s1-ova-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 07:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/getsuyoubi-no-tawawa-s1-ova-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulGetsuyoubi no Tawawa Japanese月曜日のたわわ Score6.44 ProduserNBCUniversal Entertainment Japan, i0+ TipeONA StatusFinished Airing Total Episode12 Durasi4 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 10, 2016 to Dec 26, 2016 StudioPine Jam GenreSlice of Life, Ecchi   The anime follows a salaryman who has a chance meeting with a girl named Ai on the train. They begin to meet every Monday on the train, with the man serving as her bodyguard on the crowded commute while they chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Komi San Wa Komyushou Desu</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/komi-san-wa-komyushou-desu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 05:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/komi-san-wa-komyushou-desu/</guid>
      <description>JudulKomi-san wa, Comyushou desu. Japanese古見さんは、コミュ症です。 Score8.54 ProduserHalf H.P Studio, Shogakukan TipeTV StatusOngoing Total EpisodeUnknown Durasi23 min Tanggal RilisOct 7, 2021 to ? StudioOLM GenreComedy, Slice of Life   It&#39;s Shouko Komi&#39;s first day at the prestigious Itan Private High School, and she has already risen to the status of the school&#39;s Madonna. With long black hair and a tall, graceful appearance, she captures the attention of anyone who comes across her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mushoku Tensei BD subtitle indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/mushoku-tensei-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 01:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/mushoku-tensei-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>BATCH BEDE (SOFTSUB)
 JudulMushoku Tensei: Isekai Ittara Honki Dasu Japanese無職転生 ～異世界行ったら本気だす～ Score8.36 ProduserFrontier Works, TOHO animation, Hakuhodo DY Music &amp; Pictures, BS11, Egg Firm, Kadokawa, GREE, Toho Music TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode11 Durasi23 min per ep Tanggal RilisJan 11, 2021 to Mar 22, 2021 StudioStudio Bind GenreDrama, Fantasy, Ecchi   Despite being bullied, scorned, and oppressed all of his life, a thirty-four-year-old shut-in still found the resolve to attempt something heroic—only for it to end in a tragic accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanma Baki Dual Subs Indonesia &amp; English</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/hanma-baki-dual-subs-indonesia-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/hanma-baki-dual-subs-indonesia-english/</guid>
      <description>JudulHanma Baki: Son of Ogre Japanese範馬刃牙 SON OF OGRE Score7.61 ProduserNetflix TipeONA StatusFinished Airing Total Episode12 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisSep 30, 2021 StudioTMS Entertainment GenreAction   Third part of the Baki series.
  .download-eps {font-size: 15px;font-weight: bold;padding: 10px;background: #f1f1f1;overflow: hidden;} .download-eps .smokettl {padding: 8px 10px;background: #fff;margin-bottom: 7px;} .download-eps ul {margin: 0;padding: 0;list-style: outside none none;overflow: hidden;} .download-eps ul li {margin-bottom: 7px;line-height: 31px !important;background: #fff;} .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyuuketsuki Sugu Shinu Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kyuuketsuki-sugu-shinu-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 11:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kyuuketsuki-sugu-shinu-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulKyuuketsuki Sugu Shinu Japanese吸血鬼すぐ死ぬ Score6.77 ProduserFrontier Works, Pony Canyon TipeTV StatusOngoing Total Episode12 DurasiUnknown Tanggal RilisOct 4, 2021 to ? StudioMadhouse GenreComedy, Supernatural   Vampires are said to have many weaknesses such as garlic, crosses, and sunlight. Game-loving vampire lord Draluc just so happens to be weak to... everything. He dies, turning into a pile of ash, at the slightest shock. After Vampire Hunter Ronaldo learned of a castle inhabited by a vampire rumoured to have kidnapped a kid, he went there intending to take the devil down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey Taiko Arabia Hantou De No Kiseki to Tatakai Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/journey-taiko-arabia-hantou-de-no-kiseki-to-tatakai-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/journey-taiko-arabia-hantou-de-no-kiseki-to-tatakai-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulJourney: Taiko Arabia Hantou de no Kiseki to Tatakai no Monogatari Japaneseジャーニー 太古アラビア半島での奇跡と戦いの物語 Score7.33 ProduserManga Productions TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi1 hr 49 min Tanggal RilisJun 25, 2021 StudioToei Animation, Yokohama Animation Lab GenreAction, Adventure   The Journey is a Japanese–Saudi Arabian animated film co-produced by Toei Animation and Manga Productions directed by Shizuno Koubun. The film revolves around a potter named Aws who joins a battle to defend his home city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Byousoku 5 Centimeter Dual Subs English &amp; indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/byousoku-5-centimeter-dual-subs-english-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 14:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/byousoku-5-centimeter-dual-subs-english-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulByousoku 5 Centimeter Japanese秒速５センチメートル Score7.65 ProduserUnknown TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode3 Durasi22 min per ep Tanggal RilisMar 3, 2007 StudioCoMix Wave Films GenreDrama, Romance, Slice of Life   What happens when two people love each other but just aren&#39;t meant to be together? Takaki Toono and Akari Shinohara are childhood friends, but circumstances beyond their control tear them apart. They promise to stay in contact, and although the progression of time widens the distance between them, the chain of memories remains ever-present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection Project</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/selection-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 23:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/selection-project/</guid>
      <description>JudulSelection Project JapaneseSELECTION PROJECT ScoreN/A ProduserKadokawa TipeTV StatusNot yet aired Total EpisodeUnknown DurasiUnknown Tanggal RilisOct 1, 2021 to ? StudioDoga Kobo GenreN/A   Held every summer, the national show &#34;Selection Project&#34; is the biggest gateway for girls who strive to be idols, and the place where the legendary idol Akari Amazawa was born. Suzune Miyama is also one who has longed for such a dream stage. Having been sick since childhood, she listened to the song of the light many times in her bed in the hospital room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boku No Hero Academia S5 Batch X265</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/boku-no-hero-academia-s5-batch-x265/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 06:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/boku-no-hero-academia-s5-batch-x265/</guid>
      <description>JudulBoku no Hero Academia 5th Season Japanese僕のヒーローアカデミア Score7.51 ProduserDentsu, Movic, YTV, Sony Music Entertainment, TOHO animation, Shueisha TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode25 Durasi23 min per ep Tanggal RilisMar 27, 2021 to Sep 25, 2021 StudioBones GenreAction, Comedy   UA Academy&#39;s Class 1-A has been the focus of a substantial amount of public attention due to the multiple villain attacks they have faced over the past school year. This attention has left Class 1-A&#39;s rivals, Class 1-B, feeling quite bitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JoJo No Kimyou Na Bouken Batch</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/jojo-no-kimyou-na-bouken-batch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 22:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/jojo-no-kimyou-na-bouken-batch/</guid>
      <description>JudulJoJo no Kimyou na Bouken (TV) Japaneseジョジョの奇妙な冒険 Score7.96 ProduserYomiko Advertising, Warner Bros. Japan, Kamikaze Douga, KlockWorx, Shueisha TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode26 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 6, 2012 to Apr 6, 2013 StudioDavid Production GenreAction, Adventure, Supernatural   In 1868, Dario Brando saves the life of an English nobleman, George Joestar. By taking in Dario&#39;s son Dio when the boy becomes fatherless, George hopes to repay the debt he owes to his savior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyouka Batch</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/hyouka-batch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/hyouka-batch/</guid>
      <description>JudulHyouka Japanese氷菓 Score8.12 ProduserLantis, Kadokawa Shoten, KlockWorx, chara-ani.com, Animation Do TipeTV StatusFinished Airing Total Episode22 Durasi25 min per ep Tanggal RilisApr 23, 2012 to Sep 17, 2012 StudioKyoto Animation GenreMystery, Slice of Life   Energy-conservative high school student Houtarou Oreki ends up with more than he bargained for when he signs up for the Classics Club at his sister&#39;s behest—especially when he realizes how deep-rooted the club&#39;s history really is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shinigami Bocchan to Kuro Maid Batch subtitles Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/shinigami-bocchan-to-kuro-maid-batch-subtitles-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 06:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/shinigami-bocchan-to-kuro-maid-batch-subtitles-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>.mctnx{font-size:14px;line-height:1.2em;margin-bottom:20px}.mctnx .soraddl .content,.soraddl{overflow:hidden}.mctnx .content{max-height:0;overflow:hidden;transition:max-height .2s ease-out;padding:0}.soraddl{margin-bottom:5px}.soraddl .sorattl{padding:9px 10px;background:#0c70de;border-radius:2px;cursor:pointer;line-height:0}.soraddl .sorattl:after{content:&#39;&#39;;display:inline-block;min-width:1.2em;min-height:1.2em;vertical-align:middle;float:right;background:url(&#34;data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg viewBox=&#39;0 0 24 24&#39; xmlns=&#39;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#39;%3E%3Cpath d=&#39;M8.59,16.58L13.17,12L8.59,7.41L10,6L16,12L10,18L8.59,16.58Z&#39; fill=&#39;%23fff&#39;/%3E%3C/svg%3E&#34;) center/24px no-repeat}.soraddl .sorattl h3{margin:0;font-size:inherit;display:inline-block;max-width:70%;white-space:nowrap;overflow:hidden;text-overflow:ellipsis;line-height:1.2em;color:#fff;font-weight:600}.soraddl .sorattl.collapsible.active{background:#333}.soraddl .sorattl.collapsible.active:after{background:url(&#34;data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg viewBox=&#39;0 0 24 24&#39; xmlns=&#39;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#39;%3E%3Cpath d=&#39;M7.41,8.58L12,13.17L16.59,8.58L18,10L12,16L6,10L7.41,8.58Z&#39; fill=&#39;%23fff&#39;/%3E%3C/svg%3E&#34;) center/24px no-repeat}.soraddl .soraurl{padding:4px 0;border-bottom:1px solid #ebebeb}.soraddl .soraurl a{display:inline-block;background:#f0f2f3;padding:4px 7px;border-radius:3px;margin:2px;font-size:13px}.soraddl .soraurl a:hover,.soraddl.dlone .soraurl a:nth-child(1):hover{background:#444!important;color:#fff}.soraddl .soraurl a:nth-child(1){background:#0c70de;color:#fff;font-weight:500}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl{display:flex;flex-wrap:wrap}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl .res{-webkit-box-flex:0;-ms-flex:0 0 16.66667%;flex:0 0 auto;max-height:27px;padding:4px 7px;background:#0c70de;color:#fff;font-weight:500;font-size:13px;text-align:center;border-radius:3px;margin:2px 4px 2px 0}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl .slink{flex-basis:0;-webkit-box-flex:1;flex-grow:1;max-width:100%;padding-left:0;padding-right:15px}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl a:nth-child(1){background:#f0f2f3!important;color:inherit;font-weight:400}  Episode 1-12  720p Google Drive AceFile GDrive   480p Google Drive AceFile GDrive    var coll = document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tantei Wa Mou Shindeiru Batch</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/tantei-wa-mou-shindeiru-batch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 22:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/tantei-wa-mou-shindeiru-batch/</guid>
      <description>.mctnx{font-size:14px;line-height:1.2em;margin-bottom:20px}.mctnx .soraddl .content,.soraddl{overflow:hidden}.mctnx .content{max-height:0;overflow:hidden;transition:max-height .2s ease-out;padding:0}.soraddl{margin-bottom:5px}.soraddl .sorattl{padding:9px 10px;background:#0c70de;border-radius:2px;cursor:pointer;line-height:0}.soraddl .sorattl:after{content:&#39;&#39;;display:inline-block;min-width:1.2em;min-height:1.2em;vertical-align:middle;float:right;background:url(&#34;data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg viewBox=&#39;0 0 24 24&#39; xmlns=&#39;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#39;%3E%3Cpath d=&#39;M8.59,16.58L13.17,12L8.59,7.41L10,6L16,12L10,18L8.59,16.58Z&#39; fill=&#39;%23fff&#39;/%3E%3C/svg%3E&#34;) center/24px no-repeat}.soraddl .sorattl h3{margin:0;font-size:inherit;display:inline-block;max-width:70%;white-space:nowrap;overflow:hidden;text-overflow:ellipsis;line-height:1.2em;color:#fff;font-weight:600}.soraddl .sorattl.collapsible.active{background:#333}.soraddl .sorattl.collapsible.active:after{background:url(&#34;data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg viewBox=&#39;0 0 24 24&#39; xmlns=&#39;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#39;%3E%3Cpath d=&#39;M7.41,8.58L12,13.17L16.59,8.58L18,10L12,16L6,10L7.41,8.58Z&#39; fill=&#39;%23fff&#39;/%3E%3C/svg%3E&#34;) center/24px no-repeat}.soraddl .soraurl{padding:4px 0;border-bottom:1px solid #ebebeb}.soraddl .soraurl a{display:inline-block;background:#f0f2f3;padding:4px 7px;border-radius:3px;margin:2px;font-size:13px}.soraddl .soraurl a:hover,.soraddl.dlone .soraurl a:nth-child(1):hover{background:#444!important;color:#fff}.soraddl .soraurl a:nth-child(1){background:#0c70de;color:#fff;font-weight:500}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl{display:flex;flex-wrap:wrap}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl .res{-webkit-box-flex:0;-ms-flex:0 0 16.66667%;flex:0 0 auto;max-height:27px;padding:4px 7px;background:#0c70de;color:#fff;font-weight:500;font-size:13px;text-align:center;border-radius:3px;margin:2px 4px 2px 0}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl .slink{flex-basis:0;-webkit-box-flex:1;flex-grow:1;max-width:100%;padding-left:0;padding-right:15px}.soraddl.dlone .soraurl a:nth-child(1){background:#f0f2f3!important;color:inherit;font-weight:400}  Episode 1-12  720p Google Drive AceFile GDrive   480p Google Drive AceFile GDrive    var coll = document.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
