<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>on going on FILE - WIBU</title>
    <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/tags/on-going/</link>
    <description>Recent content in on going on FILE - WIBU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 22:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://file-wibu.netlify.app/tags/on-going/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shuumatsu No Harem</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/shuumatsu-no-harem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/shuumatsu-no-harem/</guid>
      <description>JudulShuumatsu no Harem Japanese終末のハーレム Score6.62 ProduserUnknown TipeTV StatusOngoing Total Episode11 Durasi24 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 8, 2021 to ? StudioStudio Gokumi, AXsiZ GenreSci-Fi, Ecchi   The Man-Killer Virus: a lethal disease that has eradicated 99.9% of the world&#39;s male population. Mizuhara Reito has been in cryogenic sleep for the past five years, leaving behind Tachibana Erisa, the girl of his dreams. When Reito awakens from the deep freeze, he emerges into a sex-crazed new world where he himself is the planet&#39;s most precious resource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getsuyoubi No Tawawa S2 Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/getsuyoubi-no-tawawa-s2-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 01:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/getsuyoubi-no-tawawa-s2-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulGetsuyoubi no Tawawa 2 Japanese月曜日のたわわ2 Score6.86 ProduserNBCUniversal Entertainment Japan TipeONA StatusOngoing Total Episode12 Durasi6 min per ep Tanggal RilisSep 20, 2021 to ? StudioYokohama Animation Lab GenreSlice of Life, Ecchi   The anime follows a salaryman who has a chance meeting with a girl named Ai on the train. They begin to meet every Monday on the train, with the man serving as her bodyguard on the crowded commute while they chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ousama Ranking Dual Subs Indonesia &amp; English</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/ousama-ranking-dual-subs-indonesia-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 07:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/ousama-ranking-dual-subs-indonesia-english/</guid>
      <description>JudulOusama Ranking Japanese王様ランキング Score7.53 ProduserAniplex, Dentsu, Fuji TV, Kadokawa TipeTV StatusOngoing Total Episode23 Durasi23 min per ep Tanggal RilisOct 15, 2021 to ? StudioWit Studio GenreAdventure, Fantasy   The web manga centers around Bojji, a deaf, powerless prince who cannot even wield a children&#39;s sword. As the firstborn son, he strives hard and dreams of becoming the world&#39;s greatest king. However, people mutter about him behind his back as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Komi San Wa Komyushou Desu</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/komi-san-wa-komyushou-desu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 05:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/komi-san-wa-komyushou-desu/</guid>
      <description>JudulKomi-san wa, Comyushou desu. Japanese古見さんは、コミュ症です。 Score8.54 ProduserHalf H.P Studio, Shogakukan TipeTV StatusOngoing Total EpisodeUnknown Durasi23 min Tanggal RilisOct 7, 2021 to ? StudioOLM GenreComedy, Slice of Life   It&#39;s Shouko Komi&#39;s first day at the prestigious Itan Private High School, and she has already risen to the status of the school&#39;s Madonna. With long black hair and a tall, graceful appearance, she captures the attention of anyone who comes across her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyuuketsuki Sugu Shinu Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kyuuketsuki-sugu-shinu-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 11:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kyuuketsuki-sugu-shinu-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulKyuuketsuki Sugu Shinu Japanese吸血鬼すぐ死ぬ Score6.77 ProduserFrontier Works, Pony Canyon TipeTV StatusOngoing Total Episode12 DurasiUnknown Tanggal RilisOct 4, 2021 to ? StudioMadhouse GenreComedy, Supernatural   Vampires are said to have many weaknesses such as garlic, crosses, and sunlight. Game-loving vampire lord Draluc just so happens to be weak to... everything. He dies, turning into a pile of ash, at the slightest shock. After Vampire Hunter Ronaldo learned of a castle inhabited by a vampire rumoured to have kidnapped a kid, he went there intending to take the devil down.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
