<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>movie on FILE - WIBU</title>
    <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/tags/movie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in movie on FILE - WIBU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 02:15:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://file-wibu.netlify.app/tags/movie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kimi Wa Kanata</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kimi-wa-kanata/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 02:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/kimi-wa-kanata/</guid>
      <description>JudulKimi wa Kanata Japanese君は彼方 Score6.55 ProduserCUCURI TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi1 hr 35 min Tanggal RilisNov 27, 2020 StudioDigital Network Animation GenreDrama, Fantasy   Mio has feelings for her childhood friend Arata, but can&#39;t convey her feelings. One day, as they continue their delicate relationship, the two fight over something trivial. After letting tensions settle, Mio goes to make up with him in the pouring rain. While on her way, she gets into a traffic accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akira 1988 BD Subtitle Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/akira-1988-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 04:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/akira-1988-bd-subtitle-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulAkira JapaneseAKIRA（アキラ） Score8.16 ProduserMainichi Broadcasting System, Kodansha, Toho TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi2 hr 4 min Tanggal RilisJul 16, 1988 StudioTokyo Movie Shinsha GenreAction, Adventure, Horror, Sci-Fi, Supernatural   Japan, 1988. An explosion caused by a young boy with psychic powers tears through the city of Tokyo and ignites the fuse that leads to World War III. In order to prevent any further destruction, he is captured and taken into custody, never to be heard from again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violet Evergarden Movie 2020 BD HEVC</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/violet-evergarden-movie-2020-bd-hevc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/violet-evergarden-movie-2020-bd-hevc/</guid>
      <description>JudulViolet Evergarden Movie Japanese劇場版 ヴァイオレット・エヴァーガーデン Score8.88 ProduserShochiku TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode1 Durasi2 hr 20 min Tanggal RilisSep 18, 2020 StudioKyoto Animation GenreDrama, Fantasy, Slice of Life   Several years have passed since the end of The Great War. As the radio tower in Leidenschaftlich continues to be built, telephones will soon become more relevant, leading to a decline in demand for &#34;Auto Memory Dolls.&#34; Even so, Violet Evergarden continues to rise in fame after her constant success with writing letters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Byousoku 5 Centimeter Dual Subs English &amp; indonesia</title>
      <link>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/byousoku-5-centimeter-dual-subs-english-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 14:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://file-wibu.netlify.app/anime/byousoku-5-centimeter-dual-subs-english-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>JudulByousoku 5 Centimeter Japanese秒速５センチメートル Score7.65 ProduserUnknown TipeMovie StatusFinished Airing Total Episode3 Durasi22 min per ep Tanggal RilisMar 3, 2007 StudioCoMix Wave Films GenreDrama, Romance, Slice of Life   What happens when two people love each other but just aren&#39;t meant to be together? Takaki Toono and Akari Shinohara are childhood friends, but circumstances beyond their control tear them apart. They promise to stay in contact, and although the progression of time widens the distance between them, the chain of memories remains ever-present.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
